# Min Marn Oo

Singapore | S Pass



+65 8815 6448

™ minmarnoo@gmail.com

# Summary

1 year of experience working with React, Python, AWS services like API Gateway, Lambda and DynamoDB.

By no means a seasoned expert, but someone who is flexible enough to quickly adapt to new frameworks and practices in a short time frame, someone who is not hesitant to put in extra effort to get the job done in an organized and systematic manner.

### **Personal Information**

Date of Birth: 30 Sep 1993 | Nationality: Myanmar | Marital Status: Single | Available Date: 1 month note

#### **Technical Skills**

- React, NodeJS, Python, Java
- AWS Services (API Gateway, Lambda, S3, DynamoDB, etc.)
- Experience in working with RESTful APIs
- Backend development and database administration
- Serverless framework

### **Work Experience**

#### Software Engineer | Lucence

Jun 2021 - Current

- Develop and maintain frontend applications using React, Mobx and Ant Design.
- Build RESTful APIs (using API Gateway, S3, Lambda, DynamoDB and MySQL) that serves data to the frontend
- Automate report generation using Google AppScript
- Documentation of business workflow, system architecture and knowledge base.
- Setup automatic chat bot notifications on Slack using Webhooks

## IT Field Service Technologist | Micron Technology, Inc.

Jan 2019 - Jun 2021

- Configure in house software and hardware repairs
- Server preventive maintenance (disk defragmentation, administration of security and service patches)
- Perform system recovery based on incident calls and under guidance from established documents
- Manage inventory and equipments

### **Technical Specialist | Hewlett Packard Inc.**

Jun 2015 – Jan 2019

- Troubleshoot problems in non functioning equipment.
- Dismantled, adjusted, repaired and assembled equipment according to plans, blueprints, operating or repair manuals, and/or rough sketches or drawings.
- Performed equipment modification as directed by test/manufacturing engineers.
- Assisted Engineers by operating the machinery at specific settings and providing data.
- Worked under limited supervision and normally received no instructions on routine work and general instructions given for new assignments.
- Liaised with vendors regarding replacement orders and tooling modifications.

#### Education

# **Bachelor of Computing, Information Technology**

Apr 2017 – Sep 2020

University of Wollongong (SIM)

# **Diploma in Electrical and Electronic Engineering**

Apr 2012 - Mar 2015

Singapore Polytechnic

#### **Certificates**

AWS Certified: Solutions Architect - Associate

Nov 2021

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

Feb 2021